FLYNN JESSOP

Senior Full Stack Developer

SUMMARY

I am a Senior Full Stack developer orienting the long-term relationship.

I am very familiar with both of Front End and Back End Development.

Have experience with Enterprise Workflow, Web Services, Restful API services, CRM Model, E commerce Model, API Integration, online Education service, Database design,

Most of my experiences are Landing Page, WordPress, Mock-up, Web flow, E commerce Website, Shopify, Shopify Theme, SEO, Restful API, MongoDB, Modern JS Frameworks, Web Hosting, Testing Framework, GitHub, GitLab.

Love to work with Testing Framework to ensure accuracy, efficiency and responsiveness. I focus my effort on creating high performance, low resource consumption, and costeffective solutions tailored to each individual project. I always provide professional and highquality standards according to the clients' requirements.

Until now, I've completed a lot of projects:

5 E-Commerce Projects built with modern JS Framework (React, Angular, Vue)

2 Digital Product MarketPlaces built with AngularJS, Node.js and MongoDB

2 Web Applications built with React.js, Node.js and MongoDB

One Enterprize company Portal Project built with Wordpress

One Insurance brokerage site built with next.js.

One online education site built with next.js

One consumer eMarketplace site built with Laravel

One Shopify Sites built with next.js and Laravel

2 Restaruant sites built with Wordpress

One national legal recruitment firm built with Wordpress

Equipped with a client-centered design appraoch and a full-stack development toolset.

Collaborated with web designers, UX designers and back end developers to design, build, test and improve web products.

I posses a Tech Degree in Full stack Development and have 5 years building, developing and managing websites, applications.

I seek to secure the position of Full stack Developer with Orbits International and hope to share my skills, expertise and experience with valuable clients.

EXPERIENCE

Senior Full Stack Developer

03/2020 - 03/2022

Lounge Lizard

· Developed a lot of websites including an Insurance website, some eCommerce websites

Backend Developer

05/2018 - 02/2020

WEBO Digital

- · Designed and implemented scalable back end for 5 business-critical websites
- · Optimized SQL queries for the heavy-load parts of the system, which improved website responsiveness and reduced the database costs by 20%
- · Maintain and enhance existing automation tools
- · Deliver reliable, secure and efficient APIs, that are intuitive and easy to use by other developers

SKILLS

Data Analysis

Goal Settings

Independence

Project management

EDUCATION

Computer Science Charles Sturt university 2015 - 2019

LANGUAGES

English

Native

FIND ME ONLINE

Skype

live:.cid.52e88c422484a685

Telegram FJ980127

EXPERIENCE

Junior Frontend Developer

03/2017 - 04/2018

WEBO Digital

- · Developed 10+ responsive websites
- Establish user-friendly websites, including optimized check-out page, resulting in a 25% increase in user clicks and subsequently 33% in customer purchases
- · Administer front end development for 3 critical projects of the company with 100% ontime delivery while staying 7% under budget

Frontend Developer

06/2015 - 02/2017

WEBO Digital

- · Establish an interactive and dynamic website that guarantees high-traffic, page views and maximum user experience
- · Collaborated with UX/UI designers and product managers to ensure efficient and timely delivery of significant projects